Jule Wirlmann

15 Cedar St, Evens head, Australia, 0477041087, julewirlmann@outlook.de

Date of birth	12.02.1999	Nationality	Germany
Place of birth	Rendsburg		
PROFILE	Server with 3+ years of experience in food preparation and service, and a certificate in Food Handling and Safety Possesses a keen knowledge of wines, entrees, and the responsibilities of a successful restaurateur.		
	Completed biological technical assista	nt training with practical experience.	
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Mar 2017 — Feb 2020	Waitress, GVO Personal		Hannover
	•Wrote patrons' food orders on slips, memorized orders, and entered orders for transmittal to kitchen staff in a 150+ seat restaurant		
	•Cleaned all work areas, equipment, utensils, dishes, and silverware, and ensured they are stored appropriately in accordance to state law.		
	•Performed food preparation duties, such as assembling salads, appetizers, and cold dishes, portioning salads, and brewing coffee, in a fast-paced line kitchen		
Sep 2019 — Mar 2020	Allrounder, Messehof Ummel	n (Hotel)	Ummeln
	 Assisted customers by providing. detailed information, resolving their complaints, and putting smiles on their faces 		
	•Established and maintained clean and comfortable "home" environments by performing cleaning duties including vacuuming, cleaning windows, dusting, and bathrooms		
	•Greet and register guests in a 200+ ro throughout guest stays	om hotel, memorizing faces and names to ensure per	rsonalized service
Jul 2017 — Mar 2020	Tabletennis Trainer , Hannove	er 96	Hannover
	•Manage groups of up to 20 people, implement thorough warmups, program effective WODs, and supervise use of gym equipment		
	•Coached athlete at compitition		
	•Keep accurate daily attendance records and evaluate clients in personalized one-on-one training sessions		
EDUCATION			
Jun 2013 — Jul 2017	Highschool diploma, Humbuldtschule Hannover Hannover		Hannover
Feb 2018 — Feb 2020	Apprenticeship: Biological Technical Assistant, Sabine-blindow-schule		Hannover
SKILLS	Teamwork	Communication Skills	
	Ability to Organize Own Work	Time management	
	Active Learning		